goodcalculators.com 2019-10-13

# Privacy Policy

May 14, 2018

Our "Privacy Policy" applies only to our website "GoodCalculators.com" Please note, our "Privacy Policy" may be referred to as "the Policy" and "GoodCalculators.com" may be referred to as "the Website". 

## Privacy

We respect and value your right to privacy; we will not harvest any information about you, including your email address, for any reason. We will never pass on any personal information to a third party, whether for sale, rent or free of charge. 

## Cookies

We use cookies on the Website to make it an attractive environment and to increase the functionality. A cookie is simply a file that identifies a website that the server sends to your browser. Every time you visit the server, your browser will submit this cookie back to the server. 

There are two types of cookies: "persistent" and "session." Persistent cookies are kept by your browser and stay active until the expiration date set (unless you delete it prior to that). A session cookie (default cookie name is PHPSESSID) expires when you have completed your session and closed the browser. 

Web servers employ cookies so that they can identify you, track your activity on a website, and know when you return to the site. 

We use session cookies on this Website. These are only stored while you are on our Website and are deleted as soon as you leave. We do employ other types of cookies that we call "performance" or "functionality" cookies; we use these, as do some third parties with which we work, to follow the interests of our visitors. They enable us, and third parties, to analyze website use, target advertising, etc. In addition, we may also use "marketing cookies" to make ads more relevant and useful. 

You can stop cookies from being placed on your computer when you visit us by making alterations to the settings of your browser. Simply go to your browser settings and select "do not accept cookies." However, you may find that some functions on our Website will not work if you take this option. If you wish, you can visit our Website and change your cookie settings here: [Link](https://goodcalculators.com/privacy/?ez_force_cookie_consent=1). 

## Ads and Cookies

We may place advertisements and sponsored links on the Website. Usually, these will come from partner advertisers, who may offer their own privacy policy regarding their advertisements. 

The Website serves to third-party vendors and other advertisement networks. 

We store cookies so that we can personalize the content and advertisements you see on the Website. 

This is done to provide our social media features with information and to analyse the traffic that is brought to the Website.

We also store the information that we gather about how you use the Website so that we can share it with our social media, and our advertising and analytics partners. 

Third-party vendors, which include Google, use the cookies to help designate which advertisements appear to you. This is decided via which websites you visit through Google's services. 

The DoubleClick cookie feature enables Google and their partners to show advertisements based on the other website which you have visited. 

You are able to opt-out of the DoubleClick cookie by changing your [Ads Settings](https://goodcalculators.com/go/www.google.com/ads/preferences). 

## Logs

Every time a user visits our Website, we collect data on that visit in server log files. The information in these files is automatically sent to us by your browser. It includes date and time of visit, which Website you have asked for, the page you have navigated to, the user agent string (this gives us the name of the web browser and its version), and the referrer URL (which shows us where you've come from).

The data we gather is only ever used for statistical analyses and other internal processes. The data is anonymous, and there is no way to attribute it to any individual user. We do not combine this data with any other data.
